Curriculum Vitae – Anat Haimovich

Email: nice.guy.eddie.06@gmail.com

Cell: 054-6337981

Website: https://natnat16.github.io/
Github: https://github.com/natnat16

Summary

PhD in **Physical Chemistry** from Tel-Aviv University specializing in the field of solid state MAS Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR). Experienced in planning and performing experiments, conducting **computer simulations**, **data processing** and **analysis**, experienced with **MATLAB**. Highly motivated and possesses excellent technical and analytical skills.

Education

2011-2015 PhD in physical chemistry at Tel-Aviv University.

2008-2011 M.sc in physical chemistry at Tel-Aviv University.

Working in this multidisciplinary research group, required the acquisition of knowledge in the fields of physics, chemistry, biology and data analysis.

2004-2008 B.sc in Chemistry at Tel-Aviv University

Computational Skills

- Signal processing and data analysis (in NMR) using various software packages.
- Performing **computer simulations** using various software packages.
- Fitting of theoretical models to experimental data.
- Pulse sequence engineering for NMR.
- Microsoft Windows and Office.
- Familiar with programming and Linux environment.
- Programming languages: Python, MATLAB, C, C++.
- Data science: SQL ,Python and R.

Technical Skills

- Highly experienced in operation of a magic-angle spinning solid state NMR spectrometer: employing and optimizing MAS ssNMR techniques; structural characterization of biomolecules; characterization of inorganic materials.
- Protein production & characterization, Virus production & characterization.
- Preparation of metal-biomolecules complexes.
- Operation of solution NMR spectrometer.

Professional Experience

2016-2019 Lab manager in research group at Tel-Aviv University, professional and administrative management:

- Engaging in research projects.
- Scientific collaborations.
- Writing papers.
- Guidance of research students

	Guidance of research students.
2012-2014	Lab instructor in "Advanced Laboratory in Physical Chemistry" in TAU.
2011	Solution NMR measurements and analysis for "Organic Chemistry Laboratory" in TAU.
2010	Lab instructor in "General Chemistry Laboratory" in TAU.
2009-2015	Grading exercises for "General chemistry" course in TAU.
2008-2010	Lab technician in R&D Lab of Landa Laboratories Ltd.

Military Service

2000-2002 Served as a computer systems operator, was a shift manager in a facility of the

teleprocessing corps. Full service + one year in standing.

Publications

A total of 8 publications, specified below are first author papers:

- Haimovich, A. & Goldbourt, A. BBA General Subjects. 1864, 129456 (2020).
- Haimovich, A. & Goldbourt, A. J. Magn. Reson. 254, 131–138 (2015)
- Haimovich, A., Eliav, U. & Goldbourt, A. J. Am. Chem. Soc. 134, 5647–5651 (2012).

Languages

Hebrew – Native English – Excellent